City of Newburgh Urban Renewal; Collection apap375
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Administrative, 1945-2000; 1
  - Consultants 83.16E, 1983-1984 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Consulting Engineer Agreement With Milton Chazen Associates, 1977-1979 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Consulting Engineers Documents, Letters of Transmittal, Maps, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Consulting Engineers Documents, Maps, 1970-1973 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Contingencies 83.15E, 1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Contract Documents for Montgomery Street Site Improvements, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Contract for Sale of Land Newburgh Comm Development Oak Partners, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. 1 NPD- NYA 10, 1970; Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. 2-189, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Contract No. 4-189, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Contract No. A10-NYR-189, 1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Contract No. A1-NYR-189, 1969-1972; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Contract No. A2-NYA-10, 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Contract No. A3-NYA-10, 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Contract No. A4-NYA-10, 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Contract No. A5-NYR-189, 1972; Undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Contract No. A6-NYR-189, 1972; Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Contract No. A7-NYR-189, 1970-1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Contract No. A8-NYR-189, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Contract No. A9-NYR-189, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Contract No. I-189, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Contract Washington Terrace Rehabilitation, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Contract, Blooming Grove Construction, 1970 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Contract, West Industry Street, Lake Street, NDP (1 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Contract, West Industry Street, Lake Street, NDP (2 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Contract, West Industry Street, Lake Street, NDP (3 of 3), 1971-1972 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Contractors, 1975; 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Contracts for Land Redevelopment Continued, NURA, 1987-1990; Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Contracts for Sale of Land and Private Redevelopment, 1987; Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Contracts for Sale of Land and Private Redevelopment, cont'd, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Convenient Food Market Washington Terrace, 1980 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Conway, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Conway and Kilgore, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Copies of Deeds NURA to City, 1971-1976 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Copies of Mandel Resolutions and Audits NYR 189, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Copies of Newsletters, 1969-1970 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Copley Trading Co., 1973 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Copy for City Manager Urban Renewal Agency Supporting Documents, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Corporation Council, 1961; 1970 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Corresp. and Articles, 1972-1974 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence James J Hauser Jr. City Manager 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence Paul Miller re Title Reports, 1974-1976 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence/ Agendas PLK/OAK, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Cosmie and Joseph Safiotti, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Cost Estimate and Specifications work to be Done at 286 First Street, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 22)
  - Costa Beverages Transcript v. NURA and City of Newburgh, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Costa Beverages vs. NURA claim, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Costa vs. NURA Property Damage, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Costs: Acquisition, Demolition, Relocation, Undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1959 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1960 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1964 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1966 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - The Council of the City of Newburgh Proceedings, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Council Meetings, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - County Asphalt Engineering Files, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - County Asphalt Green Binder, 1973-1975 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - County Asphalt Inc., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - County Asphalt Inc. and Change Orders, 1970-1972 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - County of Orange Urban Development Program and HUD Letters, 1985-1987 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Court Decisions Legal Notes NYS Div Housing and Community Renewal, 1970-1972 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - CPC Info, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Credential Investigation Developers, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Daily Field Reports, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - DAV, 1967-1969 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - David and Lynne Walker, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 41)
  - David C and Audrey L Carey, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - David Quinn Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962; 1965-1967 (Box 64, Folder 57)
  - David Rosen, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - David Rosen Associates, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - David Tower, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - David Tower, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Debris Removal Contractors, Front and Water Streets, 1974; 1976 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - December 1970 A756-A829 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - December 1973 Relocation (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Deeds and Corresp., 1979-1982 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Deeds in Progress Parcel 3, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Deeds in Progress, 4-1-0, 1962-1963 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Deeds- Originals, 1957; 1961-1963; 1973 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Deeds: Originals Parcels 3 + 4, 1945; 1961-1962; 1967 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Defendant Exhibits, 1961-1963 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Delano Hitch Swimming Pool Davis Beacon Payroll Submission Forms-RESTRICTED, 1984 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Must consult archivist before viewing this material.
  - Demo Contract #3, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Demo Contract NYR-189 #6 Garrison, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Demo. Contracts, 1962-1966; Undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Demo. Contracts cont'd, 1963-1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Demolition Applications, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Demolition Contract Correspondence, 1962-1966 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Demolition Contract Fire Houses 63-75 Broadway, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Demolition Contract Number 3, 1967-1971 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Demolition Contract, No. 12-189, First Reformed Presbyterian Church, 104-106 Grand St., 1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Demolition Vouchers- Artko Wrecking, 1973-1974 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Dennis Maher, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Developers, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Direct Loans for NYR 189, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Direct Loans- NYA 10, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Direct Loans NYR-12, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Discriminatory Complaints, 1959; 1965-1968; 1970; 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Disposition Documents, 1969; 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Disposition Parcel #8 Grand St. 64-69 Front St., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Disposition Parcel Number 16, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Dominick Donato, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Donnaruma, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Dorothy Winstead Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Douglas Quill Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 53)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Statement Newburgh Beacon Bridge Exp., 1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Dunbar, Neal, 297 Water Street, 1961-1963 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Duncan MacDonald, MacDonald's Feed Store Relocation Payment, 1961; 1965-1966 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Dutch Reformed Church Joint Contracts, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - East End Technical Assistance Corporation, 1985 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - East Newburgh Urban Renewal Project, 1967-1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - East Newburgh Urban Renewal Project Final Project Report, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Ebenezer Baptist Church, 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Economic Development Agencies Correspondence, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Eddie Webb Barber Shop, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Edward A. Weeks, 1973-1974; 1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Edward J. Voorhis + Son, 1958 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Edward M and Betty H Rockwell 106-116 Lake St Parcel 9, 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Edwin Adams, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Electrical Specifications- Revised 97 Grand Street, 1989; Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Eliza Miller Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Elizabeth Lyons, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Ellen Smith Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 50)
  - Emily Vaughn Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Erie Railroad, 1965-1967 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Ernest Petsch, Petsch's Bakery, Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1963-1965 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Estate of Marion E Donohue and Edward Flanagan, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Estate of Mary Lee McGill Correspondence, 1970-1975 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Estimate 17-25, 27-29, Front St., 2-4-4 Lot 18-25, 1971; 1975; Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Eugene Bizzell Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1963-1965 (Box 64, Folder 42)
  - Eustance and Haravitz, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Evening News Progress Addition February 1974 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Exec Documents Demolition Pt 2, 1969-1970 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Extra Copies of Resolutions, 1972-1973 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Facade Easement, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Facade Easement 119 Liberty Street, 1981-1982 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Facade Easement 128 Liberty Street, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Facade Easement Agreements, Undated (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Facade Improvement to City- Owned, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Fakton Iron Workers, Inc., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - February 1974 Relocation (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Felicello's Grocery, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Field Inspection Forms, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Figueroa, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - File Copy Urban Renewal Agency Supporting Documents, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Finance, 1982-1985 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Financing Plan, NYR-189, 1968-1969; 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - First Amendatory Application for State Financial Assistance, 1961-1962 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - First and Second Acquisition Appraisal, 1960-1961 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - First Reformed Presbyterian Church, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - First Reformed Presbyterian Church, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - First, Liberty, Grand, Van Ness Street Specifications, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Florence DeLong, 1972-1973 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Flossie McCoy Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Flynn Appraisal Service, 1970-1972 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Flynn Contract, 1961; 1969-1973 (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Form File Condemnation Proceeding General Correspondence, 1967; 1972-1976 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Formats of Miscellaneous Documents, 1972-1974 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Forsyth Pl. Street Improvements Community Development Program, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Francis Coleman, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Francis, Louise and Charles, 1968 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Frank Jones, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Frank Konysz, 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Frank Pucino Contract #9, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Frank Thompson, 1961; 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 48)
  - Fred Herring Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Fred Young Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 44)
  - Frederick C. Hayes vs. Slater Williams, NURA and John Schoonmaker, 1976-1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Frederick E. Miles, 1977 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Fringe Benefits 83.2E, 1983-1985 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Frystak Realty Corp, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Fulton and Eggleston Financial Documents, 1948; 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Gallagher Inc., Rehab, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Gan D. Moy, 109 Montgomery Street, 1974; 1991-1992; 1994 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Garages 244-246 Water Street, 1962-1963 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Garrison Wrecking Co., Joint Contract, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Gayle, Lewis, 182 Water Street, 1962-1964 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1957 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence Blue Folder, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - General File for Gut Rehab Faade, 1980-1982; Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - General Neighborhood Renewal Plan, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - General Specifications for 238-240 Grand Street, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - George and Jennie Gordon, 1977-1978; 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - George Green 232 Water St, 4-1-4, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - George Peterson Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1966 (Box 64, Folder 61)
  - Gerald Kreisberg NYA-10, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Gilbert Sharpe Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1966 (Box 64, Folder 56)
  - Gilbert Sharpe Sharpe Barber Shop Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Golden Platter Bar, 169 Water Street, 1962-1963; 1966 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Goler Correspondence, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Goodrich, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Grace Williams Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Grand St. School + 77-79 Broadway- Mandel Closing Documents, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Grand Street Rehabilitation Projects 189, 266, 284 Grand Street, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Grant Requisitions, 1971-1976 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Green Binder- Program Participants and Departmental Staff, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Green Folder "Newburgh", 1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Grievances 1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Haims Realty Inc., 1970 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Halprin and Goler Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Halprin and Goler Original Retainer Agreement, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Harry's Supermarket, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Harvey Bros., 1972 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Harvey Burger and Luzetta Burger, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Henry and Florence Ratz, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Henry Chu Laundry, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Henry L. Schneider and Assoc., 1967-1969 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Herbert Kartiganer- Developer, 1961 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Herring, Norwood B, DBA Triego, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Hidell and Eyster, 1977-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Highland Provision Co., 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Hilda Bomar Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 41)
  - Historical Preservation Correspondence, 1967; 1969-1973 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - HL Yoh Company, 1969 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Holland and Saunders, 1970-1971 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Homeowner Contract, 1988; Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Homer Johnson, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Horan, Charles J, HHFA, 1963 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Housing Code, 1987; Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Howard Boice, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Howard Boice West Street, 1970-1971 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Howard Collins, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - HR Fountain, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - HR Fountain and Co Contract #26, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - HR Fountain and Co Inc, complete, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - HR Fountain, Appraisers: Contract, 1971-1975 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - HUD, 1981-1985 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - HUD 1981 Small Cities Pre-Application, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - HUD 6250, 6251, 1967-1968; 1971-1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - HUD and Hudson Valley Restoration Documents, 1980-1983 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - HUD Directory and Handbook, AIA Document A201 7, 1976; 1983 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - HUD Procedure Circulars, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - HUD Transactions NYA-10, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Hudson Hill Homes, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Hudson River Valley Commission, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Hudson Valley Coop, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Hudson Valley Freedom Theatre, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - IDA, HVT Bond, Sublease, Documents, etc., 1985 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - IDA, HVT Lease Agreement and Bond Documents, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - IDA, HVT Misc Corresp and Documents, 1985-1987; 1991 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - IDA, HVT Misc Corresp, Documents, Contractors, Payments, etc., 1982; 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Improvements for 92 Lander Street, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Improvements for 94 Lander Street, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Improvements to Montgomery Street from First to Second Street, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - In Rem Proceedings 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Insurance, 1957-1959 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Invitation to Bid, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Irving and Celia Zelsburg, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Irving and Joseph Weisblatt, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 42)
  - The Israel Realty Corp., 1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - J Renwick Thompson, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Jackson H. Colwell Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 34)
  - James A. Zumbo, 1961-1962 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - James B Dobbs, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - James Cassidy, 58 Second Street, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - James Cousar, 1965-1967 (Box 64, Folder 31)
  - James Harris, 26 Hasbrouch St., 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - James Ingram Candy Store, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - James J Briody, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - James Talcott Inc., 1972 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - January 1974 Relocation (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Jay S. Klein Architect, 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Jean Frankel, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Jessie Reed Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1966 (Box 64, Folder 52)
  - John Allen (Indv.) Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - John B McLean, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - John Duch Rehab, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - John Harris Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - John M Kenney Appraisal Report 3-1-1, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - John M Kenney Appraisal Report 3-1-2, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - John M Kenney Appraisal Reports, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - John Mitchell Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1961-1965 (Box 64, Folder 58)
  - John P Esposito, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - John Sartin Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1964-1966 (Box 64, Folder 59)
  - John Stillman, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - John W. Reavis, Jr., 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - John Williams, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Joseph and Amanda Rizzo, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Joseph and Amanda Rizzo, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Joseph Atkins Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Joseph Cotton Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1962-1965 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  - Joseph Zaccaria, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Joseph Zaccaria, Grocery Store, Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Jost Appraisal, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Jost Appraisal Pt 2, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Judgments, 1971-1972 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Karl Jurgens, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Kartiganen Survey Costs, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Kartiganer Associates, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Kartiganer Associates, 1972-1975 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Kartiganer Associates Montgomery Street and Wall Street, 1969-1970 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Kartiganer Associates Montgomery Street Rehab Design, 1969 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Kartiganer Associates NY 189 Disposition Surveys of Parcels, 1961; 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Kartiganer Contract Documents and Specifications, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Kartiganer Documents and County Asphalt Correspondence, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Kartiganer Herbert Contract Date January 9, 1968 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Kartiganer NYA-10, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Kartiganer NYA-10 2nd Year Engineering Lake Street, 1971-1974 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Kartiganer v. NURA Payment Voucher Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Kartiganer, Herbert Joint Contractor, 1969-1971 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Katherine Thorpe 74+76 Lake St, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Katherine Thorpe Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Kathryn Ballard 227 Water Street, 1964-1965 (Box 64, Folder 45)
  - Key Bank Leverage Agreement, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Key Bank Parcel 5B, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Key Bank, Parking Gar, Maple Bldg, Contractors, Payroll, etc.-RESTRICTED, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Knopf, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Knopf, Hymen and Ruth, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Kornblum, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Kuprych, 1970-1973 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Kuprych Bros., 1973 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Kurt R Grebe, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - LacPac Realty Corp, 1970-1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Lafayette Industrial Center, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - LaFayette Industrial Center, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Lake St Infirmary Parcels 1 and 1A, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Lake St. Misc, 1980-1981; 1984; 1987 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Lake St. U-Turn Construction + Miron Home Center Access, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lake Street, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Lake Street, 1975-1986 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Lake Street Acquisition, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Lake Street Appraisals and Correspondence, 1962; 1968-1970 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Lake Street City Project, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Lake Street Construction and Neuss Construction Inc, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Lake Street Construction Corporation, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lake Street Disposition, 1970-1973; 1977 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Lake Street Extension, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Lake Street Finance, 1970; 1974 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Lake Street Improvements between Washington Terrace and Broadway, 1980 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Lake Street Notes, 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Lake Street Planning, 1970-1974 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Lake Street Project NY A10 Phase Two Sales Book, 1966-1970 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Lake Street Site Improvements, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lakpac Realty Corp, 166-190 Lake St, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Land Disposition Arguments and Deals, 1985-1986 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Land Disposition Report NYR-12, 1985 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Land Use/ Devel Plans 1966, 1974; 1985-1989 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Lander and Broadway Street Specifications with Digital Photographs, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Lander Street Faade Easement Program 72 and 74 Lander Street, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Lander Street Faade Photographs, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lander Street Rehab Bid Opening March 18, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Lander Street Rehabilitation, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Lander Street Rehabilitation pt. 2, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Lander Street Rehabilitation 70 Lander Street, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Lander Street Rehabilitation 93 Lander Street, 1981 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Landscape Architect Documents, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Larkin Ice and Cold Storage 92-104 Lake Street, 1970-1972 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Larkin Ice and Cold Storage Corporation, 1971 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Lawson M. Louise 269 Water Street, 1962 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - LDA Deed Lake Street, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - LDA Industrial NYA-10, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - LDA June 19, 1987 CM to Chestnut (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Lead Base Paint, 1987-1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ledgers, 1962 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Ledgers, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Legal Data Application Third Year NDP Project, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Legal Notices Regarding Chestnut Partners Parcel 3 and 4, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Legal Notices Regarding Chestnut Partners Parcel 5A, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Leo Israel and Company Report, 1972-1974 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Leo Rayford Relocation Adjustment Payment, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 54)
  - Leonard Robinson City Marshall, 1969; 1971 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Leonard Sarinsky, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)